♪ In the not too distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal who wants
to rule the world ♪
♪ She threw a few things in her purse ♪
♪ And in her rocket ship she hunts him ♪
♪ All across the universe ♪
- [Pearl] I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Crow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♪
(slamming)
(beeping)
(buzzing)
- Hi everyone.
Welcome to the satellite of love.
As you can, see there's
been some changes in Thomas.
A little difficult to explain so--
- Oh, not difficult at all, Mike.
Acting on same ancient urge
imprinted in my very genes,
a few days ago I wriggled my way
onto a twig and began
squeezing a thin stream
of liquid from my spinnerette
which I turned into a soft button of silk.
Then using wave like movements of my body,
I rolled my skin off toward my rear
exposing the soft front
parts of the pupa--
- Okay, okay, okay, alright.
The point is--
- I'm a butterfly and
a glorious one at that.
- Right, so the Tom Servo
we've all known and loved--
- Oh, nothing but a larva, Mike,
and it was a surprise to me too.
Hell, I didn't even
know I had a spinnerette
until I began squeezing that thin stream
of liquid, you know?
- Okay, enough with the thin stream.
Now the coloring, is that
a camouflage of some sort?
- Uh yeah, well, unfortunately I blend in
only with myself, Mike.
Makes me incredibly susceptible
to being eaten by a barn swallow.
I tend to survive only a day or two.
- Yeah well, until that happens I
whipped up a little nectar for you.
Here you go.
- Oh boy.
(whistling)
Hey, my proboscis
doubles as a party favor.
- Neat.
We'll be right back.
- Give me some.
That's good nectar.
(upbeat music)
- Hey, Servo.
What happened to your--
- I'm still a beautiful butterfly, Mike.
I've had a few unfortunate happenstances
such as my wings being torn
off in an industrial accident.
That depressed me so I
ate a lot of Mallomars
and gained all the weight back.
But I was soon feeling better
and went back to work but alas, someone
turned on the extruitar
while I was cleaning it
and my bottom two pairs
of delicate butterfly legs
were ripped from me.
Again depressed, I hit
the pecan sandies hard
and gained my remaining weight back
and my remaining arms.
Arms by now in a metabolic frenzy
started to leech fats from my antennae
which made them so thin as to be invisible
but I am still a
beautiful butterfly, Mike,
and butterflies are free to fly.
Fly away, high away, bye bye.
(humming)
- Well makes sense.
- And I still have my proboscis.
- Ah, right.
Oh, Pearl's calling.
And it seems urgent.
Yes, Ms. Forrester.
- [Pearl] Mike, what are you doing?
It's 10 o'clock.
- [Brain Guy] You don't have
your penguin costumes on yet.
- [Bobo] We said we would
meet here at 10 o'clock
with our penguin costumes on already.
- [Pearl] Hurry up and get 'em on.
We haven't much time.
Hurry!
(mumbling)
- Hey, it's not our fault.
It's Mike's. Yeah, why
didn't you tell us, Mike?
- Yeah, that's great.
Mike didn't tell us, yeah!
- Yeah, yeah, you couldn't
even have left us a note
on the refrigerator door?
- We don't have a refrigerator.
- Exactly, Mike.
We don't have a refrigerator
'cause you don't make
enough money to get one
'cause your job stinks 'cause you
never stayed in school.
- 'Cause you were too lazy
to get proper post-secondary
school training
so we have to suffer for it.
- Exactly.
That's why it's your fault we don't
have our costumes on.
- Mike's fault.
- [Pearl] Stop talking nonsense!
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- [Bobo] Before it's too late!
- [Brain Guy] In the
name of all that is good
and decent, gentlemen, put
on your penguin costume!
- Sorry, Pearl, these old costumes
were all we could come up with.
Sorry.
(baaing)
I think we're ready.
(laughing)
- Nelson, you guys are total rubes!
- I can't believe they fell for it!
- I've never met anyone as gullible
as you poor dopes!
- To be pulled in by such
a simple thing like this!
All we had to do is call 53 costume shops
to find one that had
three penguin costumes,
reserve 'em eight months in advance
with a huge cash deposit,
then pay the balance
of 899 dollars per costume
to rent 'em for an hour,
then put 'em on, then
wait til you guys woke up
and finished breakfast, then call you
and make believe we had
set an appointment up
for you to wear penguin costumes
and then y'all fell for it!
It was so simple!
- Actually it was a titch
pathetic of us, I'm afraid.
- It was.
- Well.
Well you guys should be
even more humiliated.
Nelson, you have a dog costume on.
(laughing)
- Ha, ha, ha!
You all have ridiculous
looking penguin costumes on.
- And you're out a lot of money and time.
Burned you, man!
(laughing)
- I hereby decree that you
are more burned than us!
Your humiliation is at least 1% higher.
We win!
To celebrate, we're sending
you a horrible, smelly movie.
It's called The Screaming Skull.
Eat it!
- We're so stupid!
(crying)
(laughing)
- Boy do they look stupid.
- Yeah, at least we
maintained our dignity.
(buzzing)
- Whoa, movie's on!
(clanking)
(whirring)
- [Mike] Way better than theirs.
Get that for you.
- [Tom] Robot rump?
Ah, I was hoping it would
be about robot rumps.
- Damn.
- [Narrator] On Saturdays,
Gumby used toy robots
to do his chores so that
he and his pal Pokey
could relax.
But on this day, something
unexpected happened.
- [Mike] Gumby was nude.
- Mother, may we both
have a glass of milk?
- [Mom] You certainly may.
- One of my classmates died
in the kiln today, mother.
- [Tom] The nice thing about Gumby
is that you can use him as window caulk.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Mom] Are you getting
your work done alright?
- Look out the window, mother.
- [Tom] Pokey left a big
surprise in your begonias.
- [Mom] Well I declare.
That was a clever idea.
- This way we don't have
to hire illegal immigrants.
- [Mom] But remember to return the robots
when you're through with them.
- Sure mother.
- [Tom] Don't you worry your
squishy little head about it.
- Hey, don't!
That's Wallace and Gromit's yard!
- [Mike] Hey, that's old girl's clay.
(beeping)
- Habitat against humanity.
♪ 16 tons and what do you get ♪
- [Mike] Clay figures go home.
- Rump.
- [Mom] Such clever boys certainly
deserve some crackers with their milk.
- [Tom] Crackers, wow!
Maybe they can have white rice later!
- [Mike] Close ups reveal the
weakness of the whole premise.
- Gumby, look!
- Damn, I need more pig's blood.
(gasping)
- [Tom] Ms. Gumby is stacked.
- Gumby!
- Yes, mother?
(laughing)
- I want you to--
(gasping)
Help!
- [Mike] Yeah, we'll have to
take this down to the shop.
- Well you use one
of those older Phillip's analog chips
in your robot, you're gonna get this.
- Gumbo!
- [Tom] So he just goes to work starkers?
- Fire department.
Oh, right away dear.
- [Mike] I'll use the company car.
(siren wailing)
- [Tom] Right away, dear.
- [Crow] It's a fair (mumbling) day.
- [Tom] Gumbo sentenced to
wear permanent bell bottoms.
- [Gumbo] Are you alright, dear?
- You came just in time.
- What the?
- [Mike] Ah, you're kind of slacking off
on the house shaking here, Ron.
(beeping)
- I'm gonna set you on
Don Knotts strength.
- [Tom] Oh in the name
of all that is clay.
- [Mike] Better mow the shag carpeting.
- That squares my breasts.
- [Gumbo] Anybody hurt?
- No, but go to the garage quickly.
(beeping)
- [Mike] Mom threatened
to make me into a bowl.
- Look Gumby, your father
didn't stop that one.
- [Tom] Wonder why the Gumby's
never had any other children.
- Uh-oh.
- [Mike] My tail is lifting.
- Gotta move this body back upstate.
- Oh Gumbo, look at my flower bed!
- [Tom] I'm gonna glaze
your backside, young man.
- Bad move, robots do not fight clean.
You know that, Mike.
- [Mike] Oh yeah.
- [Tom] See.
That's what you get.
- [Mike] Oh, thank goodness
for the internal genitalia.
- [Tom] Pay for my head bump surgery
and I'll get you down.
- [Mike] Son, I'll need a can of Play-Doh
to replace my butt.
- [Gumbo] There's only one way
to stop that robot now.
- [Tom] On CNN.
- Gumbo a matador?
- [Mike] I think someone
just sold him a bad rug.
- [Tom] Eat death, robot!
(yelling)
Liquid metal.
Hey, you can throw things through dad!
I'm gonna get an anvil.
He's extremely high crotched.
- I bought this with the royalties
from an earlier short.
- [Mike] When did Gumby
get a class F license?
- [Tom] Oh, look at that robot!
Oh, that's disgusting!
(gagging)
- [Mike] Davey and Goliath
are moving in next door.
There goes the neighborhood.
- She's got a sweater
wrapped onto her head.
- [Tom] I pooped again.
- [Mike] My seventh day
with no food or water!
Please have mercy!
- [Tom] Ah, they hung his head!
- Now I'm ready for years of
powerful Adlerian therapy,
Mike.
- [Tom] They hung his head, oh!
This is worse than Seven!
- [Mike] Hey, his bump
is on the other side.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Wow.
- [Mike] Thank you and goodnight.
- [Tom] Shouldn't that be
under a pile of Chinese food.
- What a lovely arrangement
of popcorn balls.
- [Tom] Ah, I hate it when people die.
They make such a big deal out of it.
- I know.
- [Mike] It's like a dead
person won the Kentucky Derby.
- Al Lewis's one man show.
- [Tom] This reminds me of my
(mumbling) embalming fluid.
- Yeah.
- [Narrator] The Screaming
Skull is a motion picture
that reaches its climax
in shocking horror.
- [Mike] But we cut that.
- [Narrator] It's impact is so terrifying
that it may have an unforeseen effect.
It may kill you.
- [Tom] If you watch it
in front of a moving bus.
- [Narrator] Therefore, its producers
feel they must assure free burial services
to anyone who dies of fright
while seeing The Screaming Skull.
- Offer void in Utah,
Florida, and Arizona.
Taxes and acquisition fee not included.
Must take delivery of dealer stock.
- [Tom] Hey guys, I'm
gonna get a free coffin,
put some ice in it, feel it with beer,
have a great theme party.
That's what I'm doing.
What are you gonna do
with your free coffin?
Would you take those off?
- [Mike] Oh, sorry.
- Yep, shocking horror.
- [Tom] Brekekekex collex collex.
- [Mike] You guys might be tempted
to make a Smoke on the Water joke here
but I urge you to refrain.
- Okay.
- [Tom] Okay, who turned
up the heat in the hot tub?
(humming)
- [Mike] My Sharona.
(dramatic music)
- Yep, when you think shocking horror,
you think German oompah band music.
♪ Mazola corn goodness ♪
♪ Assistant director Maurice Vaccarino ♪
♪ Second unit photography Kenny Peach ♪
- [Mike] Good.
- Oh, I K-new a Kneubuhl one time.
Thank you!
(laughing)
Betty Jane Lane.
I knew a Peggy Sue Turnpike one time.
Thank you, thank you.
- [Mike] You're welcome.
- I knew an Alice Christy
Mack Nicol one time.
Thank you very much, good night.
- [Tom] Yes, shocking
horror arrives in style
in your 1953 Mercedes.
- [Mike] Can't get the damn
key out of the, uh, forget it.
(groaning)
- [Crow] Oh, that's tough.
- [Tom] Ah, Davenport.
- [Mike] Just need to adjust
you. There you go, fine.
- Welcome, Ms. Whitlock.
- Lovely, Eric.
- [Eric] You looked
disappointed for a moment.
- I did not, it's really lovely.
Oh, look!
- [Crow] Out of my way.
(bird cawing)
- [Mike] Help us, NBC
is after us, hide us!
- I'll bet that's the den there.
- That's right.
- [Ms. Whitlock] Is that a bedroom?
- [Tom] It could be.
(chuckling)
- Yes it is.
- Gonna be ours?
- It'll need some fixing first.
- Is there room for us?
- Yes.
Come on along, I'll show
you the rest of the house.
- [Mike] Wee.
(laughing)
(humming)
- I'm pleasant but I have issues.
- [Tom] Choir's late.
- [Mike] No black soled shoes please.
- [Eric] It's rather
forbidding now, I suppose.
Empty like this.
But it was usually this way.
- [Tom] Coated with filth.
- [Eric] Shortly after
Marion and I were married,
she removed all the furniture
her parents had left her.
This is our home she used to say
and we must choose everything carefully.
- Is he reading from a report?
- [Eric] Didn't get
very far before she died
but now that you're here,
it's gonna be lovely again.
- [Mike] And that ends my narration.
- I'll get your things
out of storage tomorrow.
They're all in town at the warehouse.
- So best of luck with our marriage.
Hope to see you again soon.
- I'll take care of that too.
- You have candles?
- Sure.
- It'll be twice as romantic.
- Speaking of being a romantic.
- [Tom] I invite you to join
me in marital intercourse.
- Forgot to carry you over the threshold.
- Clapton, look.
- [Jenni] I love you, I love you.
- [Eric] Ah Jenni.
I thought life had died out for me.
- [Mike] And this confirms it.
- Ew, gross!
- [Tom] Wanna go hunt for bugs?
- [Mike] Here, have a stick, honey.
- What's that up there?
- Oh, that's where Mickey
keeps his gardening things.
- Who's Mickey?
- The gardener.
- As previously implied.
- He's kept it up the
two years I've been away.
- By himself?
- That's right.
- Must work awfully hard.
- Oh, he and Marion
would spend hours on end
working here in the gardens
and up in the greenhouse back there.
- [Tom] What does Mickey do?
- See, he loved her very much.
Sometimes I used to wonder who she was.
My wife or Mickey's nurse maid.
You know, I don't think he
quite believes she's gone.
I think he expects her to show up one
of these mornings and scold
him for neglecting the gardens.
- You still love her don't you?
- [Mike] Hey look, you're
second choice. Accept it.
- I'm not jealous.
I'm grateful to her.
I think to have loved once, really love,
to learn how to love always.
Learning it from her,
you give again to me.
- [Tom] Look, I made a
mustache with your hair.
- I wish there was some way to thank her.
- I love you, deceased wife.
I mean Jenni.
(horn honking)
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
They're driving around the back.
- [Tom] Oh, it's the robots
I hired to do the yard work.
- Come on.
- [Mike] Get in the shot
before the jump cut occurs.
- Eric.
- I see Eric.
- We stopped by to meet your new wife.
- And you forgot your baby.
- Eric, this is a wonderful surprise.
- It's been a long time.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Reverend.
- It's good to see you, Eric.
Jenni, this is Ms. Snow.
- I'm very happy to meet you.
- Jenni, this is a lovely surprise.
- And the reverend, Mr. Snow.
- Hello my dear.
- She's sweet, Eric.
- I know.
- I happened to be going into town.
I ran into Mr. Mauer.
He told me you were getting back today.
- And we thought we'd just drop by
and bring you something for your dinner.
- How nice.
- Maybe it'll save you all the bother
of shopping while you're
trying to get settled.
- Then why don't you stay for dinner.
- Oh no, not tonight.
- No, we wouldn't think of that.
- Oh no, please say yes.
- We'd like for you to.
- It would be like old times.
- Alright, on the condition
that I do the cooking.
- You don't have to.
- [Ms. Snow] You know, I
know that but I'd love to.
- I'll bring fill dirt.
- Why, there's Mickey.
Excuse me, honey.
Mickey!
- [Mike] Hey, it's Mickey
and he's wearing pants today.
- Hey!
- [Tom] Mickey.
- Aw.
Poor Mickey.
- [Tom] He's so fine he
blows my mind, poor Mickey.
- He keeps this place up like a shrine.
- My husband loves me
mostly though, right?
- Eric told me how he loved Marion.
- Mickey's father was a gardener here
when Marion's mother was alive.
- [Mike] So lay off.
- Mickey and Marion grew up together here.
- Jenni, this is Mickey.
- Mickey's a wide awake nightmare.
- How do you do, Mickey?
I hope we'll be good friends.
- Well, Mickey?
- [Mike] Give her your
paw, that's a good boy.
- Nice to meet you.
- Well, shall we all go inside?
- Good idea.
Mickey, you remember you promised me some
of those rose cuttings.
- Nice seeing you again, Mickey.
Going to have to get you down
to the barber shop one day--
- [Mike] I like Mickey.
(clanking)
(beeping)
(slamming)
- Well mother, what should we do
with our naughty miscreants?
- I think we should give them
milk and cookies, hurray!
- Hi guys.
- Oh hi, Mike.
You're just in time to
enter our wonderful,
clay based world of whimsy and wonder.
- Where under the surface
lurks a rat's nest
of seething violence and hatred.
Wee!
- Hurray.
- Oh neat.
You wanna unpack that for me?
- Sure Mike.
Welcome to the land of our
two little clay figures,
Bowless and Horse Fly.
- What do they do?
- Well mostly they gather
lint, hair, and animal dander.
- But they share an
impassioned hatred of robots.
Move the robots up there, will you, Mike?
- In this colorful
story our two pranksters
hire some well meaning unsuspecting robots
who want nothing more
than to serve humanity
to the best of their abilities.
- And the two retched lumps of filth
carry out a campaign
of terror and savagery
on the handsome helpful robots.
- Okay, I think I see where you're going
with this, you guys.
- Good, you work the
lumps, we'll do the voices.
- Oh guys, come on. I know
you're hurting but let's just--
- Please Mike, just work the lumps!
- Okay, alright, fine.
(mumbling)
- Okay now, Mike, make the
lumps smash the robots.
Go ahead, go ahead, come on.
- Come on, Crow, come on.
Don't put yourself through this.
- No Mike, this is what
happens in the real world!
Horrid lumps of discharge
destroy beautiful innocent
robots with impunity.
Laughing all the way.
- You guys, you guys, calm down.
I tell you what, I'll make a note to Pearl
to go easy on the Gumby shorts, alright?
- Thank you, Mike.
- Dear Pearl, please go
easy on the Gumby shorts.
- Oh, can you get some
dizzy grizzlies there, Mike?
We need 'em for the
trauma we're experiencing.
- Get dizzy grizzlies for trauma they're--
We'll be right back.
(crying)
Come on, come on, soon you'll
be munching dizzy grizzlies.
Calm down.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] Well there he is, you know,
have people wised up to
hiring guys like this?
- Come on, Mike, how is
he any different than you?
Really.
- [Tom] I'll just grab
a goldfish for lunch.
- [Mike] Ah, nothing like
a bath to perk me right up.
- Well, I'd better go rotate the hostages.
- [Tom] That's all gunk
that sloughed off Mickey.
- Alright, that's done.
- [Ms. Snow] Oh stop, please, be careful!
(mumbling) darling, you'll break your leg.
- [Eric] You're doing great, Reverend.
- Don't worry.
- Good heavens.
Honestly, the two of them
are just like children.
(laughing)
- Ah, it doesn't look scary.
- Children love to hang drapes.
- I hope you have more luck in
getting your husband to mind
than I've had with mine.
- You know, you've got to admit,
it does make the room look better.
- Very well (mumbling).
For penance, you can
come help me with dinner.
Now come on.
Ed, would you keep Jenni company?
- Yes dear.
- [Mike] My wife and I
have an understanding.
- Oh man, it's like a buffet of victims.
I don't even know where to start.
- [Tom] Van Gogh's Howdy!
- No, Marion, no.
Send them away.
- [Mike] Exit stage left.
(mumbling)
- And I'm Zoroastrian and my
husband doesn't even know it.
- She's so very nice, Eric.
- Jenni.
- Yes.
- Isn't she wonderful?
- She's not at all like Marion
and I think that's for the best.
- [Tom] I went some place and I'm sad.
- You know, so many men,
when they lose a wife,
they try so hard to deny the loss
and they marry someone
exactly like the first wife.
Hardly seems fair using the living
to bring back the dead, does it?
- No, I suppose it doesn't.
(laughing)
- We make a prison for
ourselves out of the past.
At least, our sentimental wished for past.
- Ms. Snow.
- [Ms. Snow] Yes dear?
- [Mike] Shut up.
- There's something I must
tell you and the reverend.
- Well of course, Eric, what is it?
- You see, Jenni has not
had a very happy past.
- Oh?
- And talking about it or about something
that might strongly remind her of it,
she's very impressionable.
- Is there something wrong, Eric?
- No, not really.
You see.
- I bi-locate.
- She lost her parents many years ago
in a very tragic way and talking
about unhappy pasts only,
she's very impressionable.
See, I want her to be happy, Ms. Snow.
- Of course you do and so do we all.
Now how did she lose them?
- [Tom] She set them on top of the car
and then drove off.
- Well I'm not prying dear,
it's just that Mr. Snow
and I can help better
if we know something about it.
- They drowned in an accident.
- [Mike] Hi Debbie.
- Jenni saw it all.
- Thank you for the hand grenade.
- Who's Mr. Mauer?
- Mr. Mauer?
Why, he's a lawyer in town.
- Why?
- I thought no one knew we were coming.
You said you heard from Mr. Mauer.
- Well Eric wrote him.
- Why?
- He takes care of the
estate or what's left of it.
- Oh, that's right. Eric
has to see him tomorrow.
- [Mike] Why, why?
- Well Eric's co-executor of the state
along with Mr. Mauer.
You see, Marion's death was so sudden
that, well, all that's was left to Eric
was the house and these grounds.
Mr. Mauer told me that Eric
had found someone very sweet and very kind
and with whom he was very much in love.
He didn't say enough.
- [Tom] Unfortunately
that all fell through.
- [Mike] I still got it.
- How did Marion die?
- Didn't Eric tell you?
- He sat on her head.
- I think the subject's
rather painful to him.
Don't like to make him talk about it.
- [Tom] Let's just say she
was riddled with bullets.
- Would you mind telling me?
I'd like to know.
- It was a rainy day.
- [Mike] And he shot her.
- She and Mickey had been working up there
in the greenhouse.
She left him to go back to
the house for a few minutes.
- Then a lion jumped out and shot her.
At least that's what Eric said.
- The way we pieced it together
after the accident is that--
- [Tom] She got shot.
- While she was coming down this path,
apparently it began to rain very hard.
- [Tom] Then she got dead.
- She must have run along here.
We don't know of course
what happened then.
- [Mike] We should have called the police.
- Perhaps she slipped on a leaf.
The base of her skull was smashed.
- Anyway, how are you?
- It was thought that she hit her head
on the edge of this cement wall
where we're sitting and she fell in there.
She died in the water.
That's where Eric found
her 10 minutes later.
- [Tom] Dave Pruner searches for his ball.
- Marion.
Marion.
You said, you said Mickey, wait here.
(laughing)
I'm going down to the
house for just a minute.
Wait here, Mickey, you said.
And then you went away in the rain.
- [Mike] Oh, he's growing pot.
- And you didn't come back to play.
Marion, why did you--
- Get a box!
(whimpering)
- And don't forget that you and Eric
are coming for lunch
the day after tomorrow.
- We'll do better than that.
We'll come to church on Sunday as well.
(laughing)
- Getting Eric to church
is like moving a mountain.
- We'll come.
- [Reverend Snow] Come along
my dear, it's getting late.
- [Mike] Yes, you, hot stuff.
- Eric, thank you very much
for bringing Jenni into our lives.
- [Eric] Thank you for the dinner.
- [Ms. Snow] It was a
pleasure meeting you.
Good night.
- [Reverend Snow] Good night.
- [Tom] What the hell was that?
- Did you know that Jenni's very wealthy?
- Why yes, Mr. Mauer
told me in town today.
- She's not at all like Marion, you know.
She's so gentle and timid
as if she were afraid of something.
- I did have a gun in her
ribs during dinner, but--
- I knew you'd like my friends, dear.
What's this, huh?
- Just happy, that's all.
- Blech.
- So happy.
- Come on.
- [Tom] Hey, nice pad he's got there.
- Shut up.
- [Mike] I'm gonna start my own pond.
(upbeat music)
(foreboding music)
- [Mike] Ah, I could read
Paul Reiser's autobiography
over and over again.
- [Eric] How are the cots?
- [Tom] I have a headache.
- Fine.
- It was either the clown wallpaper
or the flat gray paint.
- What are you reading?
- [Mike] Avoiding the
Old Goat by Ann Landers.
- Something Ms. Snow sent over.
- Interesting.
- It was.
- [Jenni] It's called Beast in the Jungle.
- [Tom] It's about what
to expect on my honeymoon.
- It's all about a man
who waited all of his
life for something great
and wonderful to happen to him.
- Then he gets me.
- He had only one good friend.
It's a woman in whom he confided.
Then she died.
- [Mike] It's really hilarious.
- At her grave he suddenly realized
that she was the great wonderful thing
that he'd waited for all of his life.
But it was too late then.
- [Tom] Wow, too bad.
So, some?
- His memory's like a beast in the jungle,
rise up out of the past.
Overwhelm him.
- Poor fellow.
- Now let me tell you about
Norman Schwarzkopf's book.
- He doesn't know what he missed.
- [Tom] Flat drab passion
meanders across the screen.
So anyway, in the second
chapter this fellow
finds out that what he
looked for was (mumbling).
(banging)
- [Mike] Wow, that was great.
- [Tom] They skeet
shooting on the Lido deck?
- She's got mosquito netting
protecting her bosoms.
- [Mike] Oh, he's down there
on the teeter totter again.
- Eric.
- [Tom] Turns out he's setting
up tables for a card party.
(mysterious music)
- [Mike] Just beheading
rats down here, honey.
- It comes, yeah, I think she's nude now.
- [Mike] Oh come on.
- Mike, she's nude.
Can you at least give me that?
- Eric?
- [Tom] I have a papal decree to read.
- [Mike] Okay, I think
they've set enough mood.
They can move on to plot now.
- Yeah.
Mickey crawled in our bed again.
- [Tom] It's like they have
two servings of tension
that they're trying to
stretch out for seven people.
- [Mike] Windows 58.
- The only thing banging
in this house lately,
I'll tell you.
- [Tom] Oh, the film
broke and it was horrible!
- [Eric] What are you doing here?
- [Mike] Someday she'll look back on this
and worry about it.
(mumbling)
- [Jenni] Where were you?
- I heard something moving about.
- Turned out to be Deney Terio.
- [Tom] Hey, funny joke throw up.
- What is that?
Is that water?
- [Mike] No, it's my
marinated rear view mirror.
- Lily pad.
- Now you waterlilies calm down out there.
- I don't think Mickey
looks for her in the pond.
- Jenni, now stop it.
- I can't help it, Eric.
That bad feeling's come back.
- I forbid you to talk about it.
- She looked like that, Eric.
- [Tom] Gr, die, die, die!
- Jenni, Jenni.
- I can't help it, Eric.
- [Mike] I've been diagnosed cuckoo.
- Darling, you're just talking yourself
into those same old fears.
- Gotta talk about it, Eric,
I have to talk about it.
- I forbid you to talk about it now.
- You're under arrest.
- Just that with you
beside me I'm alive again.
I don't wanna be sick anymore.
- Honey, look.
Now you mustn't go on thinking like this.
- [Mike] You'll burn out your head.
- [Eric] Besides, how could
a poorly done self portrait
upset you so much?
- [Tom] Hey folks, this is my trick.
Come back here, look, I got it!
Wait, no, damn, they're gone.
- I know it was only my own fear.
It's my own guilt that
I can't get away from.
Eric, I'm sorry.
- [Mike] I got snot on your bathrobe.
- I want you to listen and
I want you to believe me.
- And I want you to sit on this candle.
- [Eric] Now you were sick
once, yes, but you were cured.
- [Tom] Maple cured and smoked.
- Mickey caused this.
You may as well know.
He does look for Marion night after night
down by that pond.
And he probably comes here afterwards.
I'm gonna speak to Mickey in the morning.
- [Mike] With a series
of grunts and whistles.
- [Eric] Don't you see?
How simply it's all explained away.
- (mumbling), Eric.
Before when I went to the hospital,
I was hearing things.
I'm hearing them again.
- What did you hear?
- Was it a gunshot or
more of a stabbing sound?
- [Jenni] High strained scream?
- High (mumbling)?
- What's that sound like?
- [Eric] Come here.
- [Tom] Come on, I want
you to unclog the toilet.
- [Mike] Can I interest
you in some defenestration?
(cawing)
- Now my dead wife will scream.
Listen to the difference.
- Sound like that?
It's all very, very real.
(mumbling)
You feeling better now?
- [Tom] I'm so bipolar sometimes.
- [Mike] Okay, go to dead, bed!
Bed.
- Mickey manufactures his own ammonia
to clean the greenhouse.
(laughing)
- [Tom] I'd like to go to bed
but there's a victim
strapped to it right now.
- Sh, sh.
- [Tom] People are trying to study.
- Night.
- Club.
- We won't be bothered with any
of Mickey's nightly visits anymore.
I forbid him to the house.
- I was just nervous last night.
I wish you wouldn't take it out on Mickey.
- No, he's a child.
He must be disciplined.
- I'd like him to feel I'm his friend.
- Why don't you do some gardening with him
while I'm in town?
If he sees you're interested,
you'll win him over quickly enough.
- Wait a minute.
- [Mike] Mickey gave me an ear.
I wonder if he knew whose it was.
- [Tom] Could you quick
proof my suicide note?
- Take a list of staples mostly.
- Are you sure you don't
wanna come in with me?
- Say no, say no, say no, say no.
- You'll get more done without me.
- Gotta see about the
lights, the phone, the bank.
The warehouse people about that furniture.
You know, that cot's just
about broken my back.
- Don't forget to see Mr. Mauer.
- I have to see him this evening.
It's a bore but I'll have to see him.
- Will you be home in time for dinner?
I'll wait for you.
- Now if I'm not, don't
you worry, darling.
Getting out of Mauer's clutches sometimes
requires an act of God.
I love you.
- [Mike] With a really deep passion,
madly do I love you dear.
- [Tom] Mickey, don't
chase the car this time.
- Mickey, how about I just
give you my underwear drawer?
- Hello Mickey.
- [Mike] Ah, bonjour my sweet.
- [Tom] I see you got a
new stain on your jacket.
- Woop, look out.
You almost cut him.
He's a handsome one isn't he?
So cuddly and warm. When
I was a little girl I used
to wanna be a caterpillar.
- I wanted that too and it worked out.
- Course I was a very little girl.
Here you go.
- [Mike] I gotta go stare
at things in my shed.
- Marion must have loved her garden.
We'll keep them lovely for her always.
You know what I'd like to do, Mickey?
- [Tom] Delouse you.
- I'd like to pick some
of the nicest flowers
and take them to her.
Would you like that?
- I like mice.
- Yes.
- Eric told me she was near here.
Could you show me where?
- [Tom] Well she's kind of all over.
- [Mike] Boy, this is fun.
- Ah, her favorite symbol.
A pyramid balanced on oranges.
(mimicking banging)
- [Tom] Help me, help me!
- [Mike] It's the Irene Ryan monument.
- You're mental, aren't you?
- That alright, Mickey?
I'm sure it was a great
loss to all of you, Mickey.
- [Tom] But we need to
get that sod in today.
- She cries.
- Cries?
- In the night.
- Dead people don't cry, Mickey.
- [Mickey] I heard her.
- [Mike] Observed her, even.
- Heard?
- Nah, maybe it wasn't her.
Anyway.
- [Tom] I had a victim in the oven.
- Mickey?
- Too bad, Tom.
(upbeat music)
- This is great.
- Hey guys, what's going on?
- Sh, quiet, Mike.
We're trying to scam a free coffin
out of those morons who made today's film.
- Yeah, free coffin if you die of fright.
I'm gonna say I died of fright
even though I haven't yet.
Then I'll just sit back and
wait for my free coffin.
(laughing)
- Yeah, some film releasing
companies are so stupid.
- [Female] American
International Pictures.
- Um yeah, I died while watching
your film Screaming Skull.
Sh, Crow, no, you're gonna ruin it.
I'd like to get my free
coffin out of the deal please.
- [Female] Okay, there
should be a code number
on that film.
Can you read that off to me?
- Code number, code number?
- Three, three, yeah, yeah.
- Three?
- [Female] Okay, that's
the stock reorder number.
The number I need begins with an L
and is followed by three digits.
- Okay, um, L333 I guess.
- [Female] Okay, is this Tom Servo.
- What?
- Yeah, yeah.
- [Female] Okay, I have you listed
as a viewer of Screaming Skull
and you say you died
during the viewing of this?
- Yeah, no, well my friend did.
- [Female] Sir, please
know how sorry we are
for your loss.
We'll try to make this
as easy as possible.
Which style of coffin would you like
for your dear friend, the
Imperial or the Rest Ever?
- It doesn't matter, look,
let's just forget the whole thing, okay?
- [Female] Sir, I know how
hard this must be for you
but if you'll bare with
us, we'll get through it.
Imperial or Rest Ever style?
- I don't know, Imperial I guess.
- [Female] Satin or velvet lining.
- Hang up, hang up!
- No, they've got my name!
Hey lady, looks like my friend is moving.
I guess he's not dead.
Why don't you just
cancel that order for me?
- [Female] I don't understand.
Your friend isn't dead?
- No, I thought he was dead but he's not.
Well look, he's up now.
He's moving around a lot.
Oh look, now he's in the triathlon.
Oh boy, he's finishing second.
It looks like he's gonna be just fine.
- [Female] Well the order's already
gone through to shipping.
You're going to have to receive it,
return it, and pay shipping both ways.
- Yeah fine, fine, goodbye.
Mike, hang up, quick.
- You guys should try pulling pranks
that don't involve lying about the dead.
- Oh right, Mike.
You come up with one then.
- Well there's gotta be one--
- Movie sign!
- Oh, we got movie sign.
I'll talk to you later.
(slamming)
(beeping)
- [Tom] Shew, boy.
- Does she have a ham halo?
- [Tom] CS Lewis fun house.
- I want all chests as covered up as mine.
(peacock crowing)
- [Mike] Oh sorry, Walt stepped on my toe.
- [Tom] Pinch lady (mumbling).
- That's her bikini.
- [Mike] I should probably
request my dental records
just in case.
- [Tom] Well I've had a big day.
- That scene brought to you
by the superfluous foundation.
- [Mike] Well, might as
well start that smut movie
I've been talking about.
- [Tom] She's wearing a man-ziere.
- Advanced face pinching.
- [Mike] What was I doing?
Oh, took my shirt off.
Yeah, I'm titillating the audience.
That's right.
- [Tom] Well I'd better
get those lemons out
and start rubbing them on my body.
- And the bra fairy queen appeared.
- [Mike] That is a power bra.
Underwires, over wires.
- [Tom] Hey Walt, check it out.
(peacock crowing)
- Oh man, a hog calling
contest right next door.
- I don't think he quite
accepts she's gone.
- She cries.
She cries at night.
- [Tom] Mickey, CNN Atlanta.
- I think he expects her to
show up one of these mornings.
- She died in the water.
- [Mike] I forgot something.
- The base of her skull was smashed.
- She didn't wanna die.
- She died in the water.
(screaming)
- Subway just pull in or?
- [Mike] A dandelion!
- [Tom] No!
- I'm gonna go down and do some putting.
- [Tom] Oh good, my snake charmer's here.
- [Mike] At least some oboe player
got a paycheck out of
all this horse hockey.
- We're just messing with you.
- [Tom] Hi, I'm Carol, your realtor.
- [Mike] Mary Tyler Moore!
♪ Smile though your heart is breaking ♪
- Oh great, Ebola.
- [Mike] I've gotta get to the bactine!
- [Tom] Whew, my bout with Holyfield
was tougher than I thought.
- [Mike] I threw a body
part up on the roof.
Can you help me?
(whimpering)
Something staying crunchy even in milk.
(leaves crumpling)
- [Tom] Is the camera still on
me? Are we still going here?
Oh we are, okay.
Can I come in, it's scary out here.
- Can we help you, movie lady?
Do you need a push or something?
- [Tom] I think there's
some of that bean dip left.
(banging)
- [Mike] Huh, good thing she's able
to see that with her remote camera
attached to the flexible hose.
- If this turns out to be her husband,
I'm just gonna return the
unused portion of this movie.
- [Mike] Scared, yeah, but
I'm getting a little bugged.
This is taking forever.
- [Tom] You know, they weren't really
expecting anybody to watch this.
Everybody was supposed to
be necking by this point
so Mike.
(puckering)
- [Mike] Get away from me.
Get out of here.
- [Tom] Might be fun.
- Remember, folks, if you die of boredom,
you do not get a free coffin, sorry.
- [Mike] Let me go put on
my turtleneck peignoir.
- [Tom] She's got the aurora
borealis in her living room.
- You know, all this time we could
have been watching an apple brown.
- [Mike] The movie that dares
to graphically depict
sometimes seeing peacocks
and sometimes not seeing peacocks.
- [Tom] Alas, poor Yorick,
she threw him well.
- Settled in a divot.
- [Mike] That skull
probably laid eggs already
so that doesn't do any good.
- [Tom] Woof.
- Well, got the skull thrown
so that's done anyway.
- [Mike] Probably should put
out the raging fire in the den.
- [Tom] Hey!
- Oh, why did my husband and I agree
to sleep in different movies?
- [Mike] Guess it grew little skull legs.
- [Tom] Skull?
Skully?
- Maybe he hired a cat to walk him around.
- [Mike] Alright, I guess
I'll just go around back
and use the pet door.
- [Tom] I guess Donna
Reed's still in there
waiting like an idiot.
- Donna Reed.
- [Tom] Stupid.
- [Mike] I have skull tosser's remorse.
- Not gonna be able to
reach the doorbell, damn.
- [Tom] I should get one
of those Russian mail order husbands.
- [Mike] So they put a tiny bit of movie
in a box and then just filled the rest
with a bunch of foam peanuts.
- This, for example.
This scene is a foam peanut.
Maybe two.
- [Tom] Please let it be Fabio.
- Didn't expect the Cutco
guy to come at two a.m.
(knocking)
- [Tom] The skull got a pack of squirrels
to knock on the door and run.
- Could she do something, like react
or decide or even just infer maybe?
- Think they hired a
pudgy little 13 year old
to noodle on his tuba too.
- [Mike] Hey, it's me, the skull.
We need to talk about a
certain me tossing incident.
- [Tom] Knocking, I forget
what you're supposed
to do when you hear that sound.
- [Mike] Gandalf's outside
scratching things on the door.
- I think this is what
Pat Nixon's life was like.
You think?
- [Tom] Hey, do me a favor.
Open the door, let him in.
(humming)
- [Mike] Okay.
(mumbling)
Martin Luther's nailing
each thesis individually.
- She had one nostril
enlarged for the role.
- [Mike] Trick or treat for calcium.
(screaming)
- [Tom] That's horrible.
Skull has been perfectly
civil through all this,
I have to say.
- [Mike] Ick.
- Oh, that was expertly done.
Play the break just right.
- [Tom] Very nice.
- [Mike] Well here I am.
How did I get over here?
- [Tom] Is there a bush
I haven't marked yet?
- Jenni.
Jenni.
Jenni, honey.
Honey.
- [Tom] You're in my cot.
(mumbling)
- It's alright, I'm right
here, I'm right here.
Lie back.
That's right, just lie back.
- Why are there scuffs
all over my prized skull?
- When you found me, what else was there?
- What do you mean what else?
- A skull.
- Jenni.
- I know there was no skull.
- Of course not.
- [Mike] There is my friend Bob Skull.
Did I mention him earlier?
- Mickey says Marion cries at night.
- Why, that childish, stupid--
(laughing)
- Don't blame him.
We both hear the peacocks.
He, out of his love for Marion,
wishes the cry to be from her.
I, out of my sickness--
- Now darling.
We've been all through
that nonsense last night.
- [Tom] Oh, there you are.
- Don't you see?
I've never imagined seeing
these things before.
To just stand there and see it.
Have it turn out to be nothing.
- Have you barked at
the moon lately, honey?
- Eric.
- [Mike] Do you like mayonnaise?
- I want you to call Dr.
Rand tomorrow in New York.
(mumbling)
I want you to take me back.
- No, Jenni.
Now it may sound selfish--
- [Tom] But I want everything for me.
- But don't you see, having
you to love I'm happy too.
I don't wanna lose that.
Now in the morning Mr. Snow will be here
and we'll tell him.
He's very comforting.
- [Mike] Yeah, Mr. Snow and then Mr. Horse
and then Mr. Mary Jane.
- I think he'll agree with me.
- About what?
- That I think it's Mickey.
- [Mike] Help.
- You see, he hated me from the first.
- [Tom] Where is she?
- Marion was his friend
and when I married her,
he thought I was taking her away from him
and now that she's dead, taken away
from him forever, I suppose
in that childish mind
of his I'm responsible for that.
- [Tom] Now we'll enter your dimension.
- And now because you're my wife
and in Marion's house, he hates you too.
- Damn, he's a good gardener.
- I don't think Mickey's responsible.
He's not quick enough or clever enough.
- Then who?
- Myself.
It's all in my own mind.
- We do need somebody else, darling.
We need somebody outside of the confusions
of our love for each other.
- [Mike] So I've hired Richard Crenna.
- Now the Reverend Snow
will be here in the morning.
- [Tom] You are a life saver.
I can't believe I ran out of holy water.
- It was in there.
- Okay, I'll climb in and you confess
through the little hole.
- Well, this much is real anyway.
Look here, Jenni.
- [Mike] A place to put your gum.
- You see, this is how
you gouged your hand.
You say you threw the skull down here
where Eric is looking.
- [Jenni] Yes.
- [Reverend Snow] Did
you find anything, Eric?
- Nothing yet.
- [Tom] Well I'll slap the
straight jacket on your wife.
- Surely, Jenni, you must agree with me
that anything as fragile as a skull
would have been smashed to bits down there
and Eric has found nothing
and to assume that the skull
could move on its own, all the way
from there to the driveway door.
Now Jenni, there's no reason for that.
- There's other skulls you can play with.
- Can't you see I agree with you?
Did Eric tell you I spent
over a year in a sanitarium?
- Eric told Ms. Snow that
you were very impressionable
but that's all.
- [Mike] You're actually nuts, huh?
- I know lots of people needing a rest
go to sanitariums.
- [Tom] Especially crazy people.
- This wasn't quite
that kind of sanitarium.
- [Mike] It was staffed by clowns.
- I grew up loving my
father and hating my mother.
Well she never knew it.
Something I kept to myself.
She was very beautiful.
- For an ugly person.
- Very gay like her.
Very much.
And I knew she resented that
I was not more like her.
I used to lie awake at
night, wish she were dead.
- [Mike] You know the gospel
speaks of losers like you.
- Well that isn't very unusual.
I understand many children
go through such a period.
- I was no longer a child.
- Oh, well it's hell for you then.
- [Jenni] One day--
- I stood by a chifferobe
and bored a priest to death.
- I got my wish.
They were both drowned.
- [Tom] I have to dry
clean my cassock don't I?
- I can still hear her scream.
I was all alone on a little beach
and all I could see
was the overturned boat
and the top of the waves and
I kept trying to reach them--
- As I held them under.
- The waves kept throwing me back.
- [Mike] Have you tried talking
to your minister about this?
- I could hear her cries no more.
Then hours later men came
and searched for the bodies.
They never found them.
- [Tom] Yeah, death's hard, ain't it?
- That's when this bad feeling started,
this feeling that if I'd really wanted to,
I could have saved them but I didn't.
- Well why didn't you?
- Did I really kill them?
- No, Jenni.
You tried.
You tried your very best.
- I didn't.
But (mumbling) begging and praying
couldn't make this feeling go away.
- [Mike] Look, what do you want from me?
- That's when they took
me to the hospital.
- [Tom] Well look, I got bingo.
- They told me I was cured.
- Jenni.
- Shut up.
- They told me I was cured.
(mumbling)
- [Mike] I found a screaming
hip bone if that helps.
- Mickey.
- [Tom] I'm rendering.
- Let's see, it's Tuesday.
Who was he stalking Tuesdays?
- Mickey!
- [Mike] It's time for
our discussion salon.
- You go on.
I'll be there in time for lunch.
- Where do you think
he's gone off to, Eric?
- Who knows about Mickey?
He might be hiding.
- You looked at Marion's grave?
- Nice wife.
- [Tom] Man my marriage
went down the crapper fast.
- [Mike] Yes, free!
I'm gonna strip down to
my shorts and watch golf.
- [Tom] Well let's see
how my poison ivy's doing.
(upbeat music)
- I think I'll slip down
to Cambodia for a minute.
- [Mike] Ah, I love my new jogging suit.
- [Tom] Saint Francis boxing pose.
Come on, come on.
- Mickey?
- She's buried underneath
a small changing tent.
- Mickey!
Mickey!
- [Tom] Mickey!
- [Eric] Mickey.
- [Tom] Having his own three legged race.
- Mickey.
Mickey!
- Ah, blow it out your ...
- [Tom] Come on, bring it
in, tough guy, come on.
Wait, in here.
Saint Francis.
- [Mike] Ah, so he checks Mickey's villa
in the south of France.
- Eric.
Did you find him?
- No.
Where's Jenni?
- She's with Ms. Snow on the patio.
Eric.
I think I should tell you
that Jenni's (mumbling)
me about the sanitarium.
- She (mumbling) you.
- Does your wife know?
- [Tom] We're not married.
- I told her Jenni was
impressionable but not (glitching).
Mr. Snow.
You can do both Jenni and me a great favor
by forgetting she ever told you that.
- [Reverend Snow] But
Eric, if it helps explain--
- It explains nothing.
- If I were you, Eric, I'd take her away.
If she's still impressionable
and that house frightens her so much,
why subject her to it?
- Look, I can't do a thing like that.
Be the worst thing for her.
Mr. Snow, it would be
admitting she was sick again.
I want her to be happy.
- [Mike] Mr. Slush.
- We'll stay here.
- Perhaps you know best, Eric.
- I've got a simple and old
fashioned piece of philosophy.
The only cure for her fear
is to teach her she's loved.
I mean really loved.
- I mean really, really.
- I love her so much.
- God bless you for that, Eric.
She's a very fortunate
woman having someone
like you to care for her.
- [Tom] But if you ever
need to swap wives,
just let me know.
- Be night soon.
- Oh Jenni, Jenni.
- [Mike] What, it'll be night soon.
(laughing)
- Darling, you've got to believe.
It will not happen again ever.
- [Tom] Why did you call me Donna?
- [Eric] Mickey.
Mickey!
- [Jenni] Eric, Eric!
- [Tom] Don't touch Mickey.
You don't know where he's been.
- [Mike] Mickey's trying to
lead 'em away from his eggs.
(grunting)
- [Tom] You're it!
- What are you trying
to do with that skull?
- Stop it, it wasn't his fault!
- Where did you get it?
- Leave him alone!
- I'll take care of this, Jenni.
Now I know you don't like me, Mickey.
I know you've been wanting
to get us to leave here.
This idiotic attempt to scare us
as if we were children.
It was you, wasn't it?
Wasn't it?
- No, not me, not me!
- [Mike] And I dunno.
- Get out of here, get out of here!
- [Tom] Should I consider
that my employee review?
- [Mike] I'm gonna go back
and work for Leona Helmsley.
- I wish you'd apologize to him.
You know as well as I
do it's not his fault.
It's all in my own mind.
- Jenni.
- I've got your number.
- I'm gonna do something and
you're gonna help me do it.
- [Tom] Make canapes.
- What's that?
- That portrait upstairs.
It reminds you of your mother.
- [Mike] Chair made by Gateway Computers.
- Yes.
- You were fine until you saw it.
Now it has you all preoccupied
with memories of the past.
- [Tom] You're nuttier than a cheese log.
- We're gonna burn it.
- It's precious to you, Eric.
- The picture means nothing to me.
I want you to be happy.
- And dead.
- We can't be until this
fear is out of our lives.
- [Tom] Hi, I'm Hedda Hopper.
- [Mike] I'll just brush it
with a little olive oil first.
- See, we get this done, we've
got the day to chase Mickey.
- [Tom] Okay honey, now
lay against the painting
and light it.
- Alright Jenni.
Go on, Jenni.
- [Mike] Throw the M80.
- [Tom] If you imagine
it's a Leroy Neiman,
the scene plays a lot better.
- [Mike] Oh yeah.
- Please don't do this!
Hang me in a Comfort Inn!
(screaming)
- [Mike] Someone's radio
saw went through a nail.
- It's only the peacocks.
- [Tom] Yeah, their machining
some tools out back.
- And always, scary tuba music.
- [Tom] Hello.
- [Mike] Pepe Le Pew walked by.
- Fire's almost out.
- [Tom] Yeah, we'll have to
put you in to keep it going.
- Yes.
Can't let those ashes stand over night
and the brush in these
hills are a tinder box.
- So I'm going pole
vaulting is what I'm saying.
- [Eric] You wanna help me?
- [Mike] Oh, I've been waiting for you
to ask me to rake ashes with you.
- You feeling better?
- Ah, you read me like a book, honey.
- It's as if I destroyed
her with my own hands.
- [Tom] We'll have to advance
to my burning small animals therapy.
- She'll come back here.
She'll come back.
- Darling, if you go on talking that way,
you destroy the whole purpose.
Now the thing is out of
the house and it's over.
You just give it half a chance
and you'll begin to forget it.
(clanking)
(beeping)
- Okay, you set, you got the plan down?
- I think so.
I'm a skull.
I sit here and be a skull.
Yeah, I think I got it.
- Yeah, and then to cap it all off,
Mike walks in like a sap and,
oh wait, here he comes.
(shouting)
- Ah!
(laughing)
- Hey, hey, Mike, what are you doing?
Stop hitting me with those chips!
Ow, ow!
- Man, that guy is spooky, huh?
- Yeah, he was really
hitting me with those things.
- Yeah, I think he was really,
oh no, oh no. Crow, look out!
- What, what is it?
(screaming)
- Mike, no, you're gonna kill him!
What are you doing, Mike!
What are you doing, stop it now!
Geez.
- Oh, is he gone?
- Yeah, I think so. I think
he might be out of, oh no,
for God's sake, Mike, no!
- What has he got, what does he have?
- Mike, listen to me!
Listen to the sound of my voice, Mike!
Mike, no!
Mike, this is not a skull.
This is Crow, Mike, this is Crow here.
Do you understand me, Mike?
No Mike, no, please, it's Crow.
There, put it down.
Oh no, Mike, don't hit
him with the driver!
(screaming)
Let me see that.
Is that a 10.5 loft?
- Don't talk to him about the big--
(mumbling)
- Mike, no, Mike!
Crow!
Mike, stop!
It's Crow, it's Crow, it's Crow!
It's Crow, it's Crow, it's Crow.
This is Crow, this is Crow.
- He was screaming, he's a
skull and he was screaming.
- Yes, Crow screamed, get it?
- I screamed, Mike, it's Crow.
It's all in fun.
(laughing)
Good time?
Just me screaming.
Now, now listen.
(yelling)
(screaming)
- Stay your hand, Mike!
No!
(mumbling)
(chattering)
(upbeat music)
- Why don't you just spread
those ashes out a little for me.
I'll get the water to it.
- Come on, rake, what do I pay you for?
- That's it.
- [Tom] Therapy,
counseling, bunch of hooey.
This is the real way to mental health.
(laughing)
- Eric!
- [Mike] My name's not Eric, ma'am.
- What is it, darling?
- The skull, the skull!
- Now there's no skull there.
There's no skull there, darling.
There is no skull there, Jenni.
- [Mike] Is there a skull there?
There's a skull there.
- The skull.
- [Tom] It worked.
Hey thanks, skull, come on inside.
I'll write you out that check.
- [Mike] Nothing better
than fresh roasted skull.
- I'll give you something to
scream about, young skull.
- [Mike] I ain't sharing this with no one.
- I'd scare Mickey with it
but he's got a pile of
'em under his bed already.
- [Tom] I'll cover this with candle wax
and give it back to that hippie.
- [Mike] Alright, here's the plan.
You run a short pattern into the flat.
- The skull emits a steady stream
of chlorine all day keeping
your swamp sanitary.
- [Tom] Okay, fetch boy.
Oh wait, I don't have a dog.
- Look, a large biped squirrel.
- [Tom] I'm fertilizing
the bushes as we speak.
- [Mike] Wanna go downstairs?
- Gonna be able to catch a plane tonight?
- When we get into town,
I'll call Mr. Mauer.
He'll arrange a midnight plane.
- Thought there'd be more time.
Time for (mumbling) wonderful thing.
- It's gonna be alright.
- We have our volunteer clowning
at the children's hospital.
- Of course.
(knocking)
- It's just me.
- [Tom] Brought some cool
ranch flavored hosts.
- It's gonna be alright.
- First year of marriage is
always the most psychotic.
- [Reverend Snow] Good evening, my dear.
- Hello.
- Ms. Snow (mumbling) thought you might
like some fresh eggs for your
breakfast in the morning.
- [Mike] They're hers.
- [Reverend Snow] Hello Eric.
- This is a surprise.
- Those hens labored
mightily as you can see.
- Fine, I'll take them.
- [Tom] Come on, I got the
stuff out back. Come here.
- [Reverend] You'll excuse me, dear.
- Of course.
- What is it, Eric?
- Her parents drowned
in a tub full of eggs.
- I've gotta take Jenni away.
That hospital she was in before.
- It happened again?
- I thought it would help her
if we got rid of that portrait.
You know the one.
- Yeah.
- [Mike] Dogs playing poker, yes.
- We burned it.
She saw a skull in the ashes.
- You were there?
- I saw nothing of course.
- Of course.
- I thought it was Mickey
but when I was there myself and I saw her.
- [Tom] I felt (mumbling).
- [Eric] Mr. Snow, there's
something I've never told you.
I've never told anybody.
- I married Heck Ramsay.
- When Jenni was put
away in that hospital--
- [Mike] I'd steal her jello.
- She tried to do away with herself.
I'm terribly afraid.
- You think she might try it again.
- I know she will unless I
get her back to that hospital.
- When are you going?
- Tonight.
- We shall miss you.
Ms. Snow and I have
grown very fond of Jenni.
- Yes and she of you.
- I don't suppose you'll be
coming back here again, Eric.
- No.
Never.
- Meanwhile, inside the reference head,
a fire raged on.
- I'll miss him and his wife.
He's very kind.
- Yes.
- [Mike] For a sky pilot anyway.
- I said goodbye to him just now.
He tried to talk me out of what I saw.
- How?
- [Tom] How?
- He said he felt the skull was real.
He's gonna bring some men in the morning
to search the estate.
- Where?
- He's doing Juan Epstein.
- Everywhere.
- [Mike] Who?
- He's just talking, trying to be kind.
- I suppose.
- [Tom] Yep, I suppose.
- I'll go upstairs and pack.
- Leave room for your body, honey.
- Do you wanna come with me?
- Be up in a minute.
- [Mike] Remember tonight's
our monkey love night.
- [Tom] If I can just make
it to the compost heap.
- Clothes from the Fred Rogers collection.
- [Mike] From now on
I'm gonna keep my skull
and easy store it.
- [Tom] Let's see here.
Hey, there's the rock I crushed
my first wife's skull with.
That brings back memories.
- Oh yuck, Mickey goes in there.
- [Mike] There's a
euglena holding the skull
behind his back laughing.
- This is where Evian
bottles all its water.
- [Eric] Mickey, Mickey!
- [Tom] Mickey!
- Mickey!
Come on, I just wanna borrow a towel.
- Mickey.
Theme.
Mickey's theme.
Mickey's theme, Mickey's
theme, Mickey's theme.
- [Tom] You killed the
spireas, you bastard!
- Where's that skull?
You saw me put it in
the pond, you must've.
Where is it?
- I don't know, don't know.
- Don't lie to me!
- [Tom] Ow, my mouth.
- Where is it?
- Don't know.
- Tell me the truth!
- [Mike] Don't hit me, Moe!
- [Tom] Come on, porcupine.
- [Mike] Ow, ow, hey!
- I didn't take it, didn't take it!
- Who, who?
- Not me, not me!
- Who?
- Marion, Marion took it.
Marion took it!
- Marion!
- That went better than
I thought it would.
- [Mike] Man, this is almost as bad
as when I gardened for Jackson Brown.
- Sir, you wanna borrow one of mine?
- [Tom] Maybe I'm too formal when I swim.
- [Mike] It's Mr. McFeely's music.
- [Tom] Busy day, busy day.
(shouting)
- Is this movie sponsored by
the wicker basket council or?
- [Tom] The union for dangerous
urine stained gardeners
is gonna hear about this.
- [Mike] Spork, spork,
spork, spork, spork.
- Well, I suppose you
screwed up the murder
of your second wife, too.
I told you you'd never amount to anything.
Why can't you kill properly
like the other husbands?
- [Tom] Now its music by the mutants
from beneath the planet of the apes.
- [Mike] I'm gonna see if
Mickey'd eat this for a quarter.
- Man, I gotta hire a
wife killing service.
It's cheaper in the long run really.
- [Tom] Don't you make that
skull face at me, missy.
- [Mike] William S. Burroughs.
- But Eric said that he didn't see it
when Jenni saw it.
- I know.
- Why could Eric lie like that?
- Mickey, those other
times with the skull.
Did you do it?
- No.
- Mickey, you've never lied to me before.
Lying is a sin, you understand that?
- [Tom] No.
- You must not lie to me now.
Did you do it, Mickey,
all those other times?
- No.
- I simply do not understand.
If it wasn't Mickey.
- And it wasn't her imagination.
- But why would Eric do such a thing?
- I don't know, I just don't know.
- What do you think we should do about it?
- We're going back there to that house.
- Mickey, get in the trunk.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Well, I'll go
hunting for night crawlers.
That always makes me feel better.
- Let's see, have I
worried about everything
I should have worried about today?
Have I worried about the grass?
No, no, and the trees.
Have I worried about the trees?
And the air, I forgot
to worry about the air.
- [Jenni] Mickey?
- [Mike] This movie's original
title was Looking For Mickey.
- [Tom] Step in the bear trap, come on,
step in the bear trap.
- She's strolling by Wife Skull Lake.
(whistling)
- [Mike] If Ed Wood had
directed Rules of the Game.
- I love stalking my wife.
I think it's normal and healthy.
- [Tom] Yeah, we have
a pretty good marriage.
Been three days, I haven't killed her yet.
- Mickey?
Eric and I are leaving, Mickey.
- [Mike] We left you a bowl of kibbles.
- I'd like to say goodbye.
- [Tom] And I'd like to say celery.
- I'd like to leave as
your friend, Mickey.
- [Mike] But your extremely creepy
and have very dangerous BO.
- [Jenni] Mickey?
- Every time they leave, Mickey
crawls under the basement steps.
- [Jenni] Mickey.
- [Tom] Hermione Gingold,
what are you doing here?
(screaming)
- [Mike] Oh, that gown was so tacky.
I'm actually frightened.
- Whoa, nice move.
She moves like Gail Sayers, man.
- [Tom] Well apparently he
killed a cross dressing beekeeper as well.
(panting)
- [Tom] Whoa, prairie dog.
Carrie Takano is drunk again.
- I'm gonna lasso me that chipmunk.
- [Mike] Oh Popeye.
- [Tom] Nice stride on that ghost.
(screaming)
- Kathy's trying on another bathing suit.
- [Tom] Ack.
- [Mike] Their furniture
still hasn't arrived.
That's a subplot that
just hasn't gone anywhere.
- Yeah.
- [Tom] You left the toilet seat up, ah!
- Oh great, she's playing
her Yoko Ono albums.
- [Mike] I think the title was supposed
to be Screaming semicolon Skull.
- [Tom] Oh relax honey, here,
let me massage your epiglottis.
(screaming)
- This is generally regarded as a less
than healthy form of
expression in a marriage.
(knocking)
- [Mike] It's the society
for unstrangled wives.
- [Tom] Oh, I'll get it I guess.
- Now Mike, you gotta be fair.
This movie is more than
people looking for Mickey.
At least a third of it
is doors being knocked on
and not answered.
- [Mike] Yeah, I see your point.
- [Tom] My new wife is early.
- [Mike] They need some
sofa sized art on that wall.
- So this movie is kind of a combination
of Tell Tale Heart, (mumbling)
and a piece of lint I guess.
- [Mike] It's the show us your live wife
and win a million dollars people.
- [Tom] Bad timing.
- [Tom] Can I borrow some flesh?
- Friends are visiting from hell.
(whirring)
(mumbled singing)
- Man, he just scooped a stool right up
and threw it at her.
It's a hard stool.
He should at least use some
stool softener if he's gonna--
- [Mike] Okay, okay, okay.
(screaming)
- Everyone knows it's slink skull.
(lightning cracking)
- [Mike] Ah, the Tibetan
Freedom Concert's starting.
- [Tom] I prefer
occasional outburst skull.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Oh and he's caught in a run down.
- [Tom] Oh, attacked by a pack of skulls.
That's tough.
- Yeah, there's one skull assigned
to bite his nose and just bring him down.
- [Mike] Bugs Bunny sneaking up music.
- [Tom] It is skull season
down south you know.
- [Tom] Party!
(screaming)
- Oh, I forgot to tell
the skull, ah, nevermind.
- [Tom] It's like a
scary Benny Hill sketch.
- [Mike] See, that's a real dead head.
- [Tom] Oh Mike.
- [Mike] Well it is.
- He's being compelled to
hold a skull against his neck.
(laughing)
- [Mike] Oh, he's playing
with his beach skull.
- Buy beach skull now and
receive free beach clavicle.
- [Tom] Mono, you never
know when it's gonna strike.
- [Mike] That man, he
never finishes anything.
- I'll just tell people
that I accidentally
strangled myself against the coffee table.
- [Tom] And the moral of this story,
never get close to anyone ever.
- [Mike] Thanks for the
spontaneous tonsillectomy, honey.
- Hm, I should have married
that nice Mr. Von Bula.
- [Mike] You know, if she'd
take the dress out a little,
she could breathe.
- I don't know how to put this tent up.
- [Tom] This tragedy
could have been prevented
with furniture.
- More skulls arrive in a cab.
- [Mike] We brought a night basket.
- Jenni!
Jenni!
What happened?
- Jenni.
Jenni, are you alright?
- [Tom] You missed Steven's song.
- Jenni.
- [Mike] I was getting near the dance
of the seven veils but I only have four.
- Eric.
Eric tried--
- Where is Eric?
- [Tom] Let the length
of my face comfort you.
- I don't know.
I don't know!
- I'll find him.
- (mumbling) now be careful.
It's alright darling.
- Sh, uncle lady will take care of you.
(crying)
Sh, uncle lady is here.
- [Reverend Snow] Eric!
- [Mike] Your wife's gone mental again!
- Eric, please answer me!
Eric!
Eric.
Eric, where are you?
- [Tom] Come on, you son of a,
I mean, my son.
- [Reverend Snow] Eric!
- [Mike] Listen Eric, I
just want our basket back.
Then I'll leave.
- [Tom] You're wearing that?
- Eric.
- Good riddance you stinking atheist.
- [Mike] You know, Jenni,
this really is your fault.
- Why did he do it?
- Your money.
The question is now did
Marion die in an accident.
I suppose we'll never know.
- I wanna be the next white rock girl.
- [Mike] Get into the
anti-sex mobile here.
- [Tom] I nabbed the collection
plate so dinner's on me.
- Should we call the cops?
- [Tom] Well we didn't last
time and it seemed to work out.
- [Mike] Mm, live frogs are the best.
- They're gone.
Rest.
- [Tom] This is your colon on pork.
Any questions?
- The only end, my friend.
- [Mike] Yeah, yeah, and the
children are all insane, right?
(clanking)
(beeping)
(dinging)
- Gee, I'm coming.
(mumbling)
- Hi, are you Tom Servo?
- Um, no.
(laughing)
- Well I have package here for Tom Servo
from Coffins Et Cetera.
Could you sign for it please?
- No.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Servo, your coffin is here, you luck.
- No!
- Oh hey, Tom, looks like your
coffin finally arrived, huh?
- What?
Oh, yeah, it did, didn't it?
- Here, I'll sign for that there.
- Boy, this looks like
a great place to work.
- Yeah.
- Oh, thanks, you have a good one.
- Thanks a lot, Mike.
Now I'm just gonna have
to return the thing.
Really, they stick you for the shipping.
It's like 750 bucks each way.
- Really?
Ouch, huh?
- Tell me about it. I had
to max out your optima card.
(laughing)
- I have a feeling you're gonna get a lot
of use out of that coffin.
- Oh yeah, come on sunshine.
- Hey, there's an ape calling us.
- Oh my goodness, Mike, Crow, Servo.
Why aren't you in your monkey costume?
It's getting late and you're supposed
to be in your monkey costumes now
'cause remember, we
agreed this is the time
when you should be in your
monkey costumes at this time.
(laughing)
Psych!
It's me, Bobo!
I'm kidding you!
I really had you going there for a while.
You thought I was an ape!
I totally fried you losers!
(laughing)
- Brain Guy, would you mind?
- Oh I couldn't possibly.
Oh alright.
- Hey!
You guys got big!
What the!